AMIR MABOOD

Node.js developer

+905546405389

Konyaalti, Antalya, Turkey 405389 amirm8170

Antalya, Tr

www.amirpronode.online



EXPERIENCE

Fullstack project

Nasa-Practice!

i Jan 2022 - Mar 2022

Antalya, Tr

- I built a full-stack project where users are able to select their Destination Exoplanet , Rocket type , Mission Name and Launch Date then launch their mission .
- I was able to create Rocket types with parse CSV file in node.js and save it in database before server is running . upcoming tab in this project is for check launches and delete them . then you can check delete launches in history tab with red lable .this project has sound effect too and was able to use PM2 for handle requests well.
- the main technologies that I've used are React, Node.js and MongoDB.

Backend node.js development

Pong-Game

Mar 2022 - Apr 2022

Antalya, Tr

- I built a full-stack project (focus on backend) where 2 users can play Pong game each other with socket.io.
- I was able to create socket.io server on node js and client side which allows users to play each other in rooms. and run express js side by side too.
- The main technologies that I've used are socket.io, node js, express.js.

Node.js & Telegram Bot

Combo-editor

= 2022

Antalya, Tr

I built telegram bot for edit combos in PSN market . clients uploaded their combo txt file and after 3 minutes my bot editing their combo file automatic and sent them after rename file as username.txt

This bot just accepted txt file limited and was selling monthly to clients to edit their files as well as original file.

The main technologies that I've used are node.js, Telegraf.

Freelance

2020 - 2022

Antalya, Tr

Built an ecommerce webapp to sell products online. Increased company sales.

Developed a launch website in EC2 service on AWS and Boosted streaming sales.

SUMMARY

Node.js web developer and network engineer seeking back-end developer role. Over 2 years of experience building back-end components and connecting applications to web-based services. High competencies in back-end JavaScript components and database systems.unstoppable in learning and growing.

CERTIFICATES



MongoDB

MongoDB for JavaScript Developers in 2022



Freecodecamp

Back End Development and APIs in 2022



Udemy

Complete NodeJS Developer in 2022 (GraphQL, MongoDB, + more)



ZeroToMastry

Node.js developer in 2022

SKIILLS

Node.js Express.js

MongoDB AWS (EC2) Docker Git

Graphql TypeScript SQL NoSQL

Socket.io JavaScript

estAPI Cor

LANGUAGES

English Italian



EDUCATION

Azad University Computer engineering

Sept 2014 - June 2018

ZTM online university Node.js in 2022

